<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PrivaSee</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_setup">SetupActivity</string>

    <string name="lorem_ipsum" translatable="false">TERMS AND CONDITIONS\n\n
\tWelcome to PrivaSee: a Snooping Monitoring and Parental Control with Facial Verification System. It is intended to monitor unauthorized access of application access by including face detection and face verification system, it also has parental control features such as Screen Time Limit and Application Blocking intended to limit the child’s phone usage.
\n\nPrivacy Policy\n\n
\tPrivaSee collects personal information, including facial features data and usage statistics. We take the privacy and security of your personal information seriously and comply with the Data Privacy Act of 2012 (Republic Act No. 10173) and its implementing rules and regulations.
\n\nDISCLAIMER\n\n
        \tThere will be times that the facial verification system might make mistakes in detection and verification. This is due to the following factors: image quality, variation in poses or expressions, ethnicity, environmental factors such as lighting, and algorithm design.
        \n\n
        \tThere will also be constant use of camera to take photos and other processes which might increase the battery consumption.
        \n\n
        \tBy accessing or using the application, you give your explicit consent for the collection and use of your personal information and you agree to be bound by these terms and conditions (the "Terms"). If you do not agree to these Terms, you may not use the Application.
        \n\n

ENABLE PERMISSIONS \n\n
\tCamera Permission: This permission grants an application access to the device\'s camera, allowing it to capture photos more specifically the front camera. PrivaSee will only use the camera to capture images necessary for its intended function and will not use the camera for any other purposes.
        \n\n
        \tStorage Permission: This permission grants an application access to the device\'s storage, allowing it to read, write, and modify files on the device. PrivaSee will only use the storage to save and retrieve data necessary for its intended function and will not use the storage for any other purposes.
        \n\n
         \tAccessibility Service Permission: This permission grants an application access to the Accessibility Service of the device, allowing it to perform actions and read content on the screen. PrivaSee will only use the Accessibility Service to provide its intended function and will not use the Accessibility Service for any other purposes.
        \n\n
        \tAdmin Permission: This permission grants an application administrative privilege on the device, allowing it to perform tasks that require elevated permissions, such as installing and uninstalling apps, changing system settings, and accessing sensitive data. PrivaSee Software will only use the Admin Permission to provide its intended function and will not use the Admin Permission for any other purposes.
        \n\n
        FACE ENROLMENT
        \n\n\tTo register your face, click “Register” then “Capture”. The registration will take not longer than 2 minutes to capture twenty (20) images. Keep your face steady and visible on the screen as it will automatically detects your face and will be pre-processed to a desired dimension.
        \n\n\n\n\n


    </string>

</resources>